A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Soviet Studies, Record Group 3, Series 6 FA1486
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowship Records and Institutional Support, 1985-1995; 2
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Beloit College, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 759)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Bryn Mawr College, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 760)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Indiana University, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 761)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Johns Hopkins University, School of Advanced International Studies (SAIS), 1993 (Box 66, Folder 762)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Middlebury College, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 763)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Monterey Institute, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 764)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Norwich University, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 765)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 766)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Declinations - Russian - Kutztown University, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 767)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Declinations - Russian - Trinity University, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 768)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Declinations - Russian - University of Hartford, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 769)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Declinations - Russian - University of Iowa, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 770)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Ukrainian - Harvard University, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 771)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Azeri - Indiana University, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 772)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Estonian - Indiana University, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 773)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Georgian - Indiana University, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 774)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Kazakh - Indiana University, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 775)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Uzbek - Indiana University, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 776)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Azeri, Uzbek - University of California Los Angeles (UCLA), 1993 (Box 68, Folder 777)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Ukrainian - University of Pittsburgh, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 778)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Kyrgyz - University of Washington, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 779)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Tajik - University of Washington, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 780)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Tajik, Kazan Tatar, Kazakh - University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 781)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Declinations - Kazakh - University of Washington, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 782)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Declinations - Uzbek - University of Washington, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 783)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Beloit College, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 784)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Bryn Mawr College, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 785)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Indiana University, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 786)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Johns Hopkins University, School of Advanced International Studies (SAIS), 1994 (Box 68, Folder 787)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Middlebury College, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 788)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Monterey Institute, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 789)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Norwich University, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 790)
  - In Country Language Institutes - Russian - Council on International Educational Exchange (CIEE), 1994 (Box 69, Folder 791)
  - In Country Language Institutes - Russian - State University of New York (SUNY) Albany, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 792)
  - In Country Language Institutes - Russian - University of Arizona, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 793)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Ukrainian - Harvard University, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 794)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Estonian - Indiana University, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 795)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Georgian - Indiana University, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 796)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Kazakh - Indiana University, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 797)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Kyrgyz - Indiana University, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 798)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Turkmen - Indiana University, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 799)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Uzbek - Indiana University, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 800)
  - Summer Language Institutes -Azeri, Uzbek - University of California Los Angeles (UCLA), 1994 (Box 69, Folder 801)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Kazakh - University of Kentucky, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 802)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Kazakh - University of Washington, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 803)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Kyrgyz - University of Washington, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 804)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Lithuanian - University of Washington, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 805)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Tajik - University of Washington, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 806)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Uzbek - University of Washington, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 807)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Kazan Tatar - University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 808)
  - In Country Language Institutes - Armenian - University of Michigan, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 809)
  - In Country Language Institutes - Ukrainian - Pennsylvania (Penn) State University, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 810)
  - In Country Language Institutes - Ukrainian - University of Kansas, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 811)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Beloit College, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 812)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Bryn Mawr College, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 813)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Indiana University, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 814)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Johns Hopkins University, School of Advanced International Studies (SAIS), 1995 (Box 71, Folder 815)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Middlebury College, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 816)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Monterey Institute, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 817)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Norwich University, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 818)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Tatar - Arizona State University, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 819)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Georgian - George Mason University, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 820)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Ukrainian - Harvard University, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 821)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Central Asian Languages (Kazakh, Turkmen, Uzbek) - Indiana University, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 822)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Kazakh - Indiana University, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 823)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Turkmen - Indiana University, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 824)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Uzbek - Indiana University, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 825)
  - Summer Language Institutes - University of Michigan, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 826)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Central Asian Languages (General) - University of Washington, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 827)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Kazakh - University of Washington, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 828)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Kyrgyz - University of Washington, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 829)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Lithuanian - University of Washington, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 830)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Tajik - University of Washington, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 831)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Uzbek - University of Washington, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 832)
  - JCSSS - Summer Language Institutes (Non-Russian - Central Asian) - Evaluations, 1995 (Box 122, Folder 1963)
  - In Country Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Council on International Educational Exchange, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 833)
  - In Country Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Indiana University, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 834)
  - In Country Summer Language Institutes - Russian - University of Arizona, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 835)
  - In Country Summer Language Institutes - Russian - University of Kentucky, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 836)
  - In Country Language Institutes - Russian (Academic Year Program) - State University of New York (SUNY) at Albany, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 837)
  - In Country Summer Language Institutes - Ukrainian - Pennsylvania (Penn) State University, 1995 (Box 73, Folder 838)
  - In Country Summer Language Institutes - Ukrainian - University of Kansas, 1995 (Box 73, Folder 839)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Reports, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 840-841)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Non-Russian - Reports, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 842)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Reports, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 843)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Non-Russian - Reports, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 844)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Reports, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 845)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Non-Russian - Reports, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 846-847)
  - In Country Language Institutes - Russian Programs in the Former Soviet Union - Reports, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 848)
  - In Country Summer Language Institutes - Ukrainian - University of Kansas - Report, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 849)
    University of Kansas program.
  - JCSSS - Language Institutes - Award Letters (Russian, Non-Russian, Russian and Non-Russian Programs in the Former Soviet Union, 1995 (Box 74, Folder 850)
  - JCSSS - Summer Language Institutes - Declined Applications, 1994-1995 (Box 74, Folder 851)
  - JCSSS - Language Institutes Selection Panel Minutes, 1992, 1994-1995 (Box 74, Folder 852)
  - JCSSS - Language Institutes Selection Panel Notes, 1995 (Box 122, Folder 1962)
    Notes (by Susan Bronson?) on 1995 Language Institute awards and planning for 1996 panel.
  - JCSS - New Teaching Positions Program - General, 1985 - 1986 May (Box 129, Folder 2057)
    Program to Initiate New Teaching Positions in Russian and Soviet Studies. Also described as Institutional Postdoc Fellowship Program. Funded through Title VIII grant money. File includes program announcements and initial selection panel meeting (January 3, 1986).
  - JCSS - New Teaching Positions Program - General, 1986 June - 1988 (Box 130, Folder 2058)
    Program to Initiate New Teaching Positions in Russian and Soviet Studies. Also described as Institutional Postdoc Fellowship Program. Funded through Title VIII grant money.
  - JCSS - New Teaching Positions Program - Applications, 1987-1988 (Box 130, Folder 2059)
  - JCSS - New Teaching Positions in Russian and Soviet Studies, 1988-1992 (Box 74, Folder 853)
    Program announcements for 1988 and 1989. Title VIII-funded awards in 1989 to University of Missouri-Columbia (Geography) and University of North Carolina Chapel Hill (Sociology, forfeited).
  - JCSS - New Teaching Positions in Russian and Soviet Studies - Arizona State University (Religious Studies), 1990-1992 (Box 74, Folder 854)
    Award year, 1991.
  - First-Year Fellowship Program - Princeton University, Sociology, 1988-1990 (Box 74, Folder 855)
  - First-Year Fellowship Program - University of Michigan, Sociology and Anthropology, 1989-1990 (Box 74, Folder 856)
  - First-Year Fellowship Program - University of Pittsburgh, Anthropology, 1989-1990 (Box 75, Folder 857)
  - First-Year Fellowship Program - University of Texas at Austin, Sociology, 1989-1990 (Box 75, Folder 858)
  - First-Year Fellowship Program (Declination) - American University, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 859)
  - First-Year Fellowship Program - Bilaniuk, Laada - University of Michigan, Anthropology, 1990-1991 (Box 75, Folder 860)
  - First-Year Fellowship Program - Bloch, Alexia - University of Pittsburgh, Anthropology, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 861)
  - First-Year Fellowship Program - Constantine, Joy - University of Pittsburgh, Anthropology, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 862)
  - First-Year Fellowship Program - Haas, Jeffrey K. - Princeton University, Sociology, 1990-1991 (Box 75, Folder 863)
  - First-Year Fellowship Program - Khatry-Chhetri, Sharon - University of Michigan, Sociology, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 864)
  - First-Year Fellowship Program - Wolfe, Thomas - University of Michigan, Anthropology, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 865)
  - First-Year Fellowship Program - Zollner, Anne M. - University of Texas at Austin, Sociology, 1990-1991 (Box 75, Folder 866)
  - First-Year Fellowship Program - University of California Berkeley, Sociology, 1990-1992 (Box 75, Folder 867)
  - First-Year Fellowship Program - University of Michigan, Sociology and Anthropology, 1990-1991 (Box 75, Folder 868)
  - First-Year Fellowship Program - University of Pittsburgh, Anthropology, 1990-1991 (Box 75, Folder 869)
  - First-Year Fellowship Program - University of Texas at Austin, Anthropology, 1990-1991 (Box 75, Folder 870)
  - First-Year Fellowship Program - Indiana University, Anthropology, 1991-1993 (Box 75, Folder 871)
  - First-Year Fellowship Program - University of Chicago, Anthropology, 1991-1992 (Box 75, Folder 872)
  - First-Year Fellowship Program - University of Michigan, Sociology, 1991-1992 (Box 75, Folder 873)
  - First-Year Fellowship Program - University of Pittsburgh, Anthropology, 1991-1993 (Box 75, Folder 874)
  - First-Year Fellowship Program - University of Chicago, Anthropology (Forfeited), 1991-1993 (Box 75, Folder 875)
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program - Indiana University, Anthropology, 1993-1995 (Box 112, Folder 1812)
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program - University of Michigan, Anthropology, 1993 (Box 112, Folder 1813)
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program - University of Michigan, Sociology, 1993 (Box 112, Folder 1814)
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program - University of Pittsburgh, Anthropology, 1993 (Box 112, Folder 1815)
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program - Indiana University, Anthropology, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 1816)
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program - Princeton University, Sociology (Forfeited), 1994 (Box 112, Folder 1817)
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program - University of California, Lost Angeles (UCLA), Sociology, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 1818)
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program - University of Michigan, Anthropology, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 1819)
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program - University of Michigan, Sociology, 1994-1996 (Box 112, Folder 1820)
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program - Indiana University, Anthropology, 1995 (Box 113, Folder 1821)
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program - University of Michigan, Anthropology, 1995 (Box 113, Folder 1822)
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program - University of Michigan, Sociology, 1995-1998 (Box 113, Folder 1823)
    The 1995 award was deferred until the 1997-1998 academic year.
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program (Declinations) - Columbia University, Sociology, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 1824)
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program (Declinations) - University of California, Berkeley, Sociology, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 1825)
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program (Declinations) - University of Oregon, Anthropology, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 1826)
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program (Declinations) - University of Texas at Austin, Sociology, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 1827)
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program (Declinations) - University of Washington, Anthropology, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 1828)
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program (Declinations) - University of California at Los Angeles (UCLA), Sociology, 1995 (Box 113, Folder 1829)
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program (Declinations) - University of Texas at Austin, Sociology, 1995 (Box 113, Folder 1830)
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program - Selection Panel, 1995 (Box 113, Folder 1831)
  - JCSSS - First Year Fellowship Program - Award History, 1990-1995 (Box 113, Folder 1832)
  - Soviet Sociological Research Projects - Junior Program - Buckley, Cynthia, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 876)
  - Soviet Sociological Research Projects - Junior Program - Dawson, Jane, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 877)
  - Soviet Sociological Research Projects - Junior Program - Rutland, Peter, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 878)
  - Soviet Sociological Research Projects - Junior Program - Solnick, Steven, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 879)
  - Soviet Sociological Research Projects - Junior Program - Velkoff, Victoria, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 880)
  - Soviet Sociological Research Projects - Senior Program - Kingkade, W. Ward, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 881)
  - Soviet Sociological Research Projects - Senior Program - Mason, David, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 882)
  - Soviet Sociological Research Projects - Junior Program, Alternate 1 - Schluter, Daniel, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 883)
  - Soviet Sociological Research Projects - Junior Program, Alternate 2 - Johnson, Douglas, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 884)
  - Soviet Sociological Research Projects - Junior Program, Alternate 3 - Slocum, John W., 1989 (Box 75, Folder 885)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Junior Program - Amsden, Elizabeth, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 886)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Junior Program - Butterfield, James, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 887)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Junior Program - Clark, Terry Dee, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 888)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Junior Program - Cushman, Thomas, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 889)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Junior Program - Drummond, William, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 890)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Junior Program - Fish, Michael, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 891)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Junior Program - Heinemeier, Meredith M. Sample, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 892)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Junior Program - Kaiser, Kyra, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 893)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Junior Program - Marshall, Monty, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 894)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Junior Program - Petro, Nicolai, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 895)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Junior Program - Rhine, Staci, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 896)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Junior Program - Weigle, Marcia, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 897)
  - Soviet Sociological Research Projects - Senior Program, Alternate 1 - Bushnell, John, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 898)
  - Soviet Sociological Research Projects - Senior Program, Alternate 2 - Berbaum, Michael, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 899)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Senior Program - Bloombaum, MIlton, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 900)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Senior Program - Field, Mark, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 901)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Senior Program - Ignashev, Diane Nemec, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 902)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Senior Program - Jonitis, Peter Paul, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 903)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Senior Program - Van Atta, Donald, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 904)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Arnold, Anthony (Senior Program), 1990 (Box 76, Folder 905)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Badagliacco, Joanne (Junior Program), 1990 (Box 76, Folder 906)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Behar, Joseph, 1990 (Box 76, Folder 907)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Berbaum, Michael (Senior Program), 1990 (Box 76, Folder 908)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Briery, John Henry, III (Junior Program), 1990 (Box 76, Folder 909)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Feldman, Jan Lynn (Senior Program), 1990 (Box 76, Folder 910)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Gimenez, Martha E. (Junior Program), 1990 (Box 76, Folder 911)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Johnson, Katrina (Junior Program), 1990 (Box 77, Folder 912)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Kiernan, Brendan (Junior Program), 1990 (Box 77, Folder 913)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - McKeehan, Irina (Junior Program), 1990 (Box 77, Folder 914)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Markowitz, Fran (Junior Program), 1990 (Box 77, Folder 915)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Newman, Bruce (Senior Program), 1990 (Box 77, Folder 916)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Sanjian, Andrea Stevenson (Senior Program), 1990 (Box 77, Folder 917)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Sedaitis, Judith (Junior Program), 1990 (Box 77, Folder 918)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Ta'ati, Poopak (Junior Program), 1990 (Box 77, Folder 919)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Von Wiren-Garczynski, Vera (Senior Program), 1990 (Box 77, Folder 920)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Winsor, Donna (Junior Program), 1990 (Box 77, Folder 921)
  - Soviet Sociological Research (Declinations) - Vladimirov, Zhelyu (Junior Program), 1990 (Box 77, Folder 922)
  - Workshop in Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Levenson, Marcia, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 923)
  - Workshop in Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Zawilski, Valerie, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 924)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Abramson, David, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 925)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Allen, Mary, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 926)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Bilaniuk, Laada, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 927)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Creuziger, Clementine, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 928)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Derluguian, Georgi, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 929)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Essig, Laurie, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 930)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Hrycak, Alexandra, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 931)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Karpov, Vyacheslav, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 932)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Lisovskaya, Elena, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 933)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Ries, Nancy, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 934)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Suhomlinova, Olga, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 935)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Zollner, Anne, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 936)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Phillips, Anthony (Declination?), 1993 (Box 78, Folder 937)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Allen, Howard, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 938)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Biloon, Joselyn, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 939)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Dershem, Larry, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 940)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Doggett, Suzanne, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 941)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Favreault, Melissa, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 942)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Gerber, Theodore, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 943)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Hirsch, Francine, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 944)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Ishkanian, Armine, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 945)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Lalluka, Seppo, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 946)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Rivkin-Fish, Michele, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 947)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Roberts, Sean, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 948)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Romanov, Artemi, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 949)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Wanner, Catherine, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 950)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology (Declinations) - Zollner, Anne (Alternate), 1994 (Box 78, Folder 951)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology (Declinations) - Korobkov, Andrei, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 952)